<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="105">
    <author>exekx</author>
    <manufacturer>exekx</manufacturer>
    <version>1.3.0.0</version>
    <modName>FS25_RealisticHarvesting</modName>
    <title>
        <en>Realistic Harvesting</en>
        <de>Realistisches Ernten</de>
        <fr>Récolte Réaliste</fr>
        <pl>Realistyczne Żniwa</pl>
        <es>Cosecha Realista</es>
        <it>Raccolta Realistica</it>
        <cz>Realistická Sklizeň</cz>
        <br>Colheita Realista</br>
        <uk>Реалістичний Збір Врожаю</uk>
        <ru>Реалистичный Сбор Урожая</ru>
        <hu>Realisztikus betakarítás</hu>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Adds realistic harvesting mechanics to your combines.

Features:
- Dynamic engine load calculation based on throughput (mass/sec)
- Automatic speed limiting to prevent overloading
- Visual Crop Loss indicator (LOW/MED/HIGH)
- Customizable HUD with real-time metrics
- Full multiplayer support with server-side settings
- Support for all harvest types (Grain, Forage, Roots, Cotton)
- Pickup Header support (Swathing)

Changelog 1.3.0.0:
- NEW: Completely rewritten load calculation logic based on Mass Throughput (t/h) instead of area. Fixing issues with high-yield maps causing unrealistic slow speeds.
- NEW: Added support for Pickup Headers (Swathing) - now correctly registers load based on swath volume.
- NEW: Visual Crop Loss Indicator (LOW/MED/HIGH) instead of percentages for better readability.
- IMPROVED: HUD now shows Green/Yellow/Red indicators for loss.
- IMPROVED: Adaptive smoothing for more stable speed control.

Changelog 1.2.1.0:
- Fixed productivity calculation displaying incorrect values (was 1000x too low)
- Improved accuracy of mass-to-volume conversion using actual crop density

Changelog 1.2.0.0:
- Added support for Cotton Harvesters
- Added partial support for Forage Harvesters
- Fixed Multiplayer Synchronization issues
- Fixed settings menu conflict with other mods
- Improved Unit System display (Imperial/Metric)

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- New Feature: Added "Reset Settings" button to settings menu footer (key: X)
- UI Improvements: Added side descriptions for all settings in menu (tooltips)
- Localization: Full translation support for 10 languages (EN, DE, FR, PL, ES, IT, CZ, PT-BR, UK, RU)
- Bug Fixes: Improved settings menu stability]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Fügt realistische Erntemechanik zu Ihren Mähdreschern hinzu.

Funktionen:
- Dynamische Motorlastberechnung basierend auf Erntedichte und Schneidwerksbreite
- Automatische Geschwindigkeitsbegrenzung zur Vermeidung von Überlastung
- Ernteverlustanzeige (nur visuell - vollständige Simulation kommt bald)
- Anpassbares HUD mit Echtzeit-Metriken
- Volle Multiplayer-Unterstützung mit serverseitigen Einstellungen
- Unterstützung für Baumwollernter, Hackfruchternter und teilweise Feldhäcksler

Changelog 1.2.1.0:
- Produktivitätsberechnung korrigiert (zeigte falsche Werte an - war 1000x zu niedrig)
- Verbesserte Genauigkeit der Masse-zu-Volumen-Konvertierung mit tatsächlicher Erntedichte

Changelog 1.2.0.0:
- Unterstützung für Baumwollernter hinzugefügt
- Teilweise Unterstützung für Feldhäcksler hinzugefügt
- Multiplayer-Synchronisierungsprobleme behoben
- Einstellungsmenü-Konflikt mit anderen Mods behoben
- Einheitensystem-Anzeige verbessert (Imperial/Metrisch)

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Neue Funktion: Schaltfläche "Einstellungen zurücksetzen" zur Fußzeile des Einstellungsmenüs hinzugefügt (Taste: X)
- UI-Verbesserungen: Seitenbeschreibungen für alle Einstellungen im Menü hinzugefügt (Tooltips)
- Lokalisierung: Vollständige Übersetzungsunterstützung für 10 Sprachen (EN, DE, FR, PL, ES, IT, CZ, PT-BR, UK, RU)
- Fehlerbehebungen: Verbesserte Stabilität des Einstellungsmenüs]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Ajoute des mécaniques de récolte réalistes à vos moissonneuses-batteuses.

Fonctionnalités:
- Calcul dynamique de la charge moteur basé sur la densité des cultures et la largeur de la coupe
- Limitation automatique de la vitesse pour éviter la surcharge
- Indicateur de perte de récolte (visuel uniquement - simulation complète à venir)
- HUD personnalisable avec métriques en temps réel
- Support multijoueur complet avec paramètres côté serveur
- Support pour moissonneuses à coton, récolteuses de racines et support partiel pour ensileuses

Changelog 1.2.1.0:
- Correction du calcul de productivité affichant des valeurs incorrectes (était 1000x trop bas)
- Amélioration de la précision de la conversion masse-volume avec la densité réelle des cultures

Changelog 1.2.0.0:
- Ajout du support pour les moissonneuses à coton
- Ajout du support partiel pour les ensileuses
- Correction des problèmes de synchronisation multijoueur
- Correction du conflit du menu des paramètres avec d'autres mods
- Amélioration de l'affichage du système d'unités (Impérial/Métrique)

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Nouvelle fonctionnalité: Bouton "Réinitialiser les paramètres" dans le pied de page du menu (touche: X)
- Améliorations de l'interface: Descriptions latérales pour tous les paramètres (infobulles)
- Localisation: Support de traduction complet pour 10 langues (EN, DE, FR, PL, ES, IT, CZ, PT-BR, UK, RU)
- Corrections de bugs: Amélioration de la stabilité du menu des paramètres]]></fr>
        <pl><![CDATA[Dodaje realistyczną mechanikę żniw do kombajnów.

Funkcje:
- Dynamiczne obliczanie obciążenia silnika w oparciu o gęstość plonów i szerokość hederów
- Automatyczne ograniczanie prędkości, aby zapobiec przeciążeniu
- Wskaźnik strat plonów (tylko wizualny - pełna symulacja wkrótce)
- Konfigurowalny HUD z metrykami w czasie rzeczywistym
- Pełne wsparcie dla trybu wieloosobowego z ustawieniami po stronie serwera
- Wsparcie dla kombajnów bawełnianych, kombajnów korzeniowych i częściowe wsparcie dla sieczkarni

Changelog 1.2.1.0:
- Naprawiono obliczanie produktywności wyświetlające nieprawidłowe wartości (było 1000x za niskie)
- Poprawiono dokładność konwersji masy na objętość przy użyciu rzeczywistej gęstości plonów

Changelog 1.2.0.0:
- Dodano wsparcie dla kombajnów bawełnianych
- Dodano częściowe wsparcie dla sieczkarni
- Naprawiono problemy z synchronizacją w trybie wieloosobowym
- Naprawiono konflikt menu ustawień z innymi modami
- Poprawiono wyświetlanie systemu jednostek (Imperialny/Metryczny)

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Nowa funkcja: Przycisk "Resetuj ustawienia" w stopce menu (klawisz: X)
- Ulepszenia interfejsu: Opisy boczne dla wszystkich ustawień (podpowiedzi)
- Lokalizacja: Pełne wsparcie tłumaczeń dla 10 języków (EN, DE, FR, PL, ES, IT, CZ, PT-BR, UK, RU)
- Poprawki błędów: Poprawiona stabilność menu ustawień]]></pl>
        <es><![CDATA[Añade mecánicas de cosecha realistas a tus cosechadoras.

Características:
- Cálculo dinámico de carga del motor basado en densidad de cultivos y ancho de cabezal
- Limitación automática de velocidad para evitar sobrecarga
- Indicador de pérdida de cosecha (solo visual - simulación completa próximamente)
- HUD personalizable con métricas en tiempo real
- Soporte multijugador completo con configuración del servidor
- Soporte para cosechadoras de algodón, cosechadoras de raíces y soporte parcial para picadoras

Changelog 1.2.1.0:
- Corregido cálculo de productividad mostrando valores incorrectos (era 1000x demasiado bajo)
- Mejorada precisión de conversión masa-volumen usando densidad real de cultivos

Changelog 1.2.0.0:
- Añadido soporte para cosechadoras de algodón
- Añadido soporte parcial para picadoras
- Corregidos problemas de sincronización multijugador
- Corregido conflicto del menú de configuración con otros mods
- Mejorada visualización del sistema de unidades (Imperial/Métrico)

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Nueva característica: Botón "Restablecer configuración" en pie de menú (tecla: X)
- Mejoras de interfaz: Descripciones laterales para todas las configuraciones (tooltips)
- Localización: Soporte de traducción completo para 10 idiomas (EN, DE, FR, PL, ES, IT, CZ, PT-BR, UK, RU)
- Correcciones de errores: Mejorada estabilidad del menú de configuración]]></es>
        <it><![CDATA[Aggiunge meccaniche di raccolta realistiche alle tue mietitrebbie.

Caratteristiche:
- Calcolo dinamico del carico motore basato su densità colture e larghezza testata
- Limitazione automatica velocità per prevenire sovraccarico
- Indicatore perdita raccolto (solo visivo - simulazione completa in arrivo)
- HUD personalizzabile con metriche in tempo reale
- Supporto multiplayer completo con impostazioni lato server
- Supporto per raccoglitrici cotone, raccoglitrici radici e supporto parziale per trincia

Changelog 1.2.1.0:
- Corretto calcolo produttività che mostrava valori errati (era 1000x troppo basso)
- Migliorata precisione conversione massa-volume usando densità reale colture

Changelog 1.2.0.0:
- Aggiunto supporto per raccoglitrici cotone
- Aggiunto supporto parziale per trincia
- Corretti problemi sincronizzazione multiplayer
- Corretto conflitto menu impostazioni con altri mod
- Migliorata visualizzazione sistema unità (Imperiale/Metrico)

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Nuova funzionalità: Pulsante "Ripristina impostazioni" nel piè di pagina menu (tasto: X)
- Miglioramenti interfaccia: Descrizioni laterali per tutte le impostazioni (tooltip)
- Localizzazione: Supporto traduzione completo per 10 lingue (EN, DE, FR, PL, ES, IT, CZ, PT-BR, UK, RU)
- Correzioni bug: Migliorata stabilità menu impostazioni]]></it>
        <cz><![CDATA[Přidává realistickou mechaniku sklizně k vašim kombajnům.

Funkce:
- Dynamický výpočet zatížení motoru na základě hustoty plodin a šířky žacího ústrojí
- Automatické omezení rychlosti pro zabránění přetížení
- Indikátor ztráty úrody (pouze vizuální - plná simulace brzy)
- Přizpůsobitelný HUD s metrikami v reálném čase
- Plná podpora multiplayeru s nastavením na straně serveru
- Podpora pro sklízecí stroje na bavlnu, sklízecí stroje na kořenovou zeleninu a částečná podpora pro sklízecí řezačky

Changelog 1.2.1.0:
- Opravený výpočet produktivity zobrazující nesprávné hodnoty (byl 1000x příliš nízký)
- Vylepšená přesnost převodu hmotnosti na objem pomocí skutečné hustoty plodin

Changelog 1.2.0.0:
- Přidána podpora pro sklízecí stroje na bavlnu
- Přidána částečná podpora pro sklízecí řezačky
- Opraveny problémy se synchronizací v multiplayeru
- Opraven konflikt nabídky nastavení s jinými mody
- Vylepšené zobrazení systému jednotek (Imperiální/Metrický)

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Nová funkce: Tlačítko "Obnovit nastavení" v zápatí nabídky (klávesa: X)
- Vylepšení rozhraní: Boční popisy pro všechna nastavení (nápovědy)
- Lokalizace: Plná podpora překladu pro 10 jazyků (EN, DE, FR, PL, ES, IT, CZ, PT-BR, UK, RU)
- Opravy chyb: Vylepšená stabilita nabídky nastavení]]></cz>
        <br><![CDATA[Adiciona mecânicas de colheita realistas às suas colheitadeiras.

Recursos:
- Cálculo dinâmico de carga do motor baseado em densidade de culturas e largura da plataforma
- Limitação automática de velocidade para evitar sobrecarga
- Indicador de perda de colheita (apenas visual - simulação completa em breve)
- HUD personalizável com métricas em tempo real
- Suporte completo para multijogador com configurações do servidor
- Suporte para colheitadeiras de algodão, colheitadeiras de raízes e suporte parcial para forrageiras

Changelog 1.2.1.0:
- Corrigido cálculo de produtividade exibindo valores incorretos (estava 1000x muito baixo)
- Melhorada precisão da conversão massa-volume usando densidade real das culturas

Changelog 1.2.0.0:
- Adicionado suporte para colheitadeiras de algodão
- Adicionado suporte parcial para forrageiras
- Corrigidos problemas de sincronização multijogador
- Corrigido conflito do menu de configurações com outros mods
- Melhorada exibição do sistema de unidades (Imperial/Métrico)

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Novo recurso: Botão "Restaurar configurações" no rodapé do menu (tecla: X)
- Melhorias de interface: Descrições laterais para todas as configurações (dicas)
- Localização: Suporte completo de tradução para 10 idiomas (EN, DE, FR, PL, ES, IT, CZ, PT-BR, UK, RU)
- Correções de bugs: Melhorada estabilidade do menu de configurações]]></br>
        <uk><![CDATA[Додає реалістичну механіку збору врожаю до ваших комбайнів.

Функції:
- Динамічний розрахунок навантаження двигуна на основі щільності культур та ширини жатки
- Автоматичне обмеження швидкості для запобігання перевантаженню
- Індикатор втрат врожаю (тільки візуально - повна симуляція незабаром)
- Налаштовуваний HUD з метриками в реальному часі
- Повна підтримка мультиплеєра з налаштуваннями на стороні сервера
- Підтримка бавовняних комбайнів, коренезбиральних комбайнів та часткова підтримка кормозбиральних комбайнів

Зміни 1.2.1.0:
- Виправлено розрахунок продуктивності, що показував неправильні значення (було в 1000 разів занижено)
- Покращено точність перетворення маси в об'єм з використанням реальної щільності культур

Зміни 1.2.0.0:
- Додано підтримку бавовняних комбайнів
- Додано часткову підтримку кормозбиральних комбайнів
- Виправлено проблеми синхронізації в мультиплеєрі
- Виправлено конфлікт меню налаштувань з іншими модами
- Покращено відображення системи одиниць (Імперська/Метрична)

Зміни 1.1.0.0:
- Нова функція: Кнопка "Скинути налаштування" в нижній частині меню (клавіша: X)
- Покращення інтерфейсу: Бічні описи для всіх налаштувань (підказки)
- Локалізація: Повна підтримка перекладу для 10 мов (EN, DE, FR, PL, ES, IT, CZ, PT-BR, UK, RU)
- Виправлення помилок: Покращено стабільність меню налаштувань]]></uk>
        <ru><![CDATA[Добавляет реалистичную механику уборки урожая к вашим комбайнам.

Функции:
- Динамический расчет нагрузки двигателя на основе плотности культур и ширины жатки
- Автоматическое ограничение скорости для предотвращения перегрузки
- Индикатор потерь урожая (только визуально - полная симуляция скоро)
- Настраиваемый HUD с метриками в реальном времени
- Полная поддержка мультиплеера с настройками на стороне сервера
- Поддержка хлопкоуборочных комбайнов, корнеуборочных комбайнов и частичная поддержка кормоуборочных комбайнов

Изменения 1.2.1.0:
- Исправлен расчет производительности, показывающий неправильные значения (было в 1000 раз занижено)
- Улучшена точность преобразования массы в объем с использованием реальной плотности культур

Изменения 1.2.0.0:
- Добавлена поддержка хлопкоуборочных комбайнов
- Добавлена частичная поддержка кормоуборочных комбайнов
- Исправлены проблемы синхронизации в мультиплеере
- Исправлен конфликт меню настроек с другими модами
- Улучшено отображение системы единиц (Имперская/Метрическая)

Изменения 1.1.0.0:
- Новая функция: Кнопка "Сбросить настройки" в нижней части меню (клавиша: X)
- Улучшения интерфейса: Боковые описания для всех настроек (подсказки)
- Локализация: Полная поддержка перевода для 10 языков (EN, DE, FR, PL, ES, IT, CZ, PT-BR, UK, RU)
- Исправления ошибок: Улучшена стабильность меню настроек]]></ru>
        <hu><![CDATA[Valósághű betakarítási mechanikákat ad hozzá a kombájnjaidhoz.

Funkciók:
- Dinamikus motor­terhelés-számítás a termény sűrűsége és a vágóasztal szélessége alapján
- Automatikus sebességkorlátozás a túlterhelés elkerülése érdekében
- Terményveszteség-jelző (csak vizuális – a teljes szimuláció hamarosan érkezik)
- Testreszabható HUD valós idejű adatokkal
- Teljes többjátékos támogatás, szerveroldali beállításokkal
- Támogatás gyapotbetakarítókhoz, gyökérnövény-betakarítókhoz, valamint részleges támogatás silózó betakarítókhoz

Változások 1.2.1.0:
- Javítva a teljesítményszámítás, amely hibás értékeket mutatott (1000× túl alacsony volt)
- Pontosabb tömeg–térfogat átváltás a valós terménysűrűség használatával

Változások 1.2.0.0:
- Gyapotbetakarítók támogatásának hozzáadása
- Részleges támogatás a silózó betakarítókhoz
- Többjátékos szinkronizációs problémák javítása
- Beállítási menü ütközésének javítása más modokkal
- Egységrendszer megjelenítésének javítása (Imperiális/Metrikus)

Változások 1.1.0.0:
- Új funkció: „Beállítások visszaállítása” gomb hozzáadása a beállítási menü aljához (billentyű: X)
- Felhasználói felület fejlesztések: Oldalsó leírások minden beállításhoz (tooltippek)
- Lokalizáció: Teljes fordítási támogatás 10 nyelven (EN, DE, FR, PL, ES, IT, CZ, PT-BR, UK, RU)
- Hibajavítások: A beállítási menü stabilitásának javítása]]></hu>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_FS25_RealisticHarvesting.dds</iconFilename>
    
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/main.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <l10n>
        <text name="rhm_section">
            <en>Realistic Harvesting</en>
            <de>Realistisches Ernten</de>
            <fr>Récolte Réaliste</fr>
            <pl>Realistyczne Żniwa</pl>
            <es>Cosecha Realista</es>
            <it>Raccolta Realistica</it>
            <cz>Realistická Sklizeň</cz>
            <br>Colheita Realista</br>
            <uk>Реалістичний збір врожаю</uk>
            <ru>Реалистичный сбор урожая</ru>
            <hu>Realisztikus betakarítás</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_difficulty"><en>Difficulty</en><uk>Складність</uk><de>Schwierigkeit</de><fr>Difficulté</fr><pl>Trudność</pl><es>Dificultad</es><it>Difficoltà</it><cz>Obtížnost</cz><br>Dificuldade</br><ru>Сложность</ru><hu>Nehézség</hu></text>
        <text name="rhm_difficulty_motor"><en>Engine Power Limit</en><uk>Обмеження Потужності</uk><de>Motorleistung</de><fr>Puissance moteur</fr><pl>Moc silnika</pl><es>Potencia del motor</es><it>Potenza del motore</it><cz>Výkon motoru</cz><br>Potência do motor</br><ru>Мощность двигателя</ru><hu>Motorteljesítmény</hu></text>
        <text name="rhm_difficulty_motor_short"><en>Engine Limit</en><uk>Потужність</uk><de>Motor</de><fr>Moteur</fr><pl>Silnik</pl><es>Motor</es><it>Motore</it><cz>Motor</cz><br>Motor</br><ru>Мотор</ru><hu>Motor</hu></text>
        <text name="rhm_difficulty_motor_long"><en>Determines how much extra power is available. Arcade = +100%, Normal = +20%, Realistic = 0%.</en><uk>Визначає додаткову потужність. Аркада = +100%, Норма = +20%, Реалізм = 0%.</uk><de>Bestimmt die verfügbare Zusatzleistung.</de><fr>Détermine la puissance supplémentaire disponible.</fr><pl>Określa dostępną dodatkową moc.</pl><es>Determina la potencia extra disponible.</es><it>Determina la potenza extra disponibile.</it><cz>Určuje dostupný výkon navíc.</cz><br>Determina a potência extra disponível.</br><ru>Определяет дополнительную мощность.</ru><hu>Meghatározza a többletteljesítményt.</hu></text>
        
        <text name="rhm_difficulty_loss"><en>Crop Loss Penalty</en><uk>Штраф за Втрати</uk><de>Ernteverlust</de><fr>Perte de récolte</fr><pl>Strata plonów</pl><es>Pérdida de cultivo</es><it>Perdita raccolto</it><cz>Ztráta úrody</cz><br>Perda de colheita</br><ru>Потеря урожая</ru><hu>Termésveszteség</hu></text>
        <text name="rhm_difficulty_loss_short"><en>Loss Penalty</en><uk>Втрати</uk><de>Verlust</de><fr>Perte</fr><pl>Strata</pl><es>Pérdida</es><it>Perdita</it><cz>Ztráta</cz><br>Perda</br><ru>Потеря</ru><hu>Veszteség</hu></text>
        <text name="rhm_difficulty_loss_long"><en>Determines crop loss severity when overloaded. Realistic = High penalty.</en><uk>Визначає суворість втрат при перевантаженні. Реалізм = Високий штраф.</uk><de>Bestimmt die Schwere des Ernteverlusts.</de><fr>Détermine la sévérité de la perte.</fr><pl>Określa dotkliwość strat.</pl><es>Determina la severidad de la pérdida.</es><it>Determina la gravità della perdita.</it><cz>Určuje závažnost ztráty.</cz><br>Determina a gravidade da perda.</br><ru>Определяет строгость потерь.</ru><hu>Meghatározza a veszteség súlyosságát.</hu></text>
        
        <text name="rhm_diff_1">
            <en>Arcade</en>
            <de>Arkade</de>
            <fr>Arcade</fr>
            <pl>Zręcznościowy</pl>
            <es>Arcade</es>
            <it>Arcade</it>
            <cz>Arkáda</cz>
            <br>Arcade</br>
            <uk>Аркада</uk>
            <ru>Аркада</ru>
            <hu>Árkád</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_difficulty_long">
            <en>Arcade: High limits (+100%). Normal: Moderate (+20%). Realistic: Strict (0%)</en>
            <de>Arkade: Hohe Limits (+100%). Normal: Moderat (+20%). Realistisch: Strikt (0%)</de>
            <fr>Arcade: Limites élevées (+100%). Normal: Modéré (+20%). Réaliste: Strict (0%)</fr>
            <pl>Arkada: Wysokie limity (+100%). Normalna: Umiarkowane (+20%). Realistyczna: Ścisłe (0%)</pl>
            <es>Arcade: Límites altos (+100%). Normal: Moderado (+20%). Realista: Estricto (0%)</es>
            <it>Arcade: Limiti alti (+100%). Normale: Moderato (+20%). Realistica: Rigorosi (0%)</it>
            <cz>Arkáda: Vysoké limity (+100%). Normální: Mírné (+20%). Realistická: Přísné (0%)</cz>
            <br>Arcade: Limites altos (+100%). Normal: Moderado (+20%). Realista: Rigorosos (0%)</br>
            <uk>Аркада: Високі ліміти (+100%). Нормальна: Помірні (+20%). Реалістична: Жорсткі (0%)</uk>
            <ru>Аркада: Высокие лимиты (+100%). Обычная: Умеренные (+20%). Реалистичная: Строгие (0%)</ru>
            <hu>Könnyű: Magas korlátok (+100%). Normál: Mérsékelt (+20%). Realisztikus: Szigorú (0%)</hu>
        </text>
        

        
        <text name="rhm_diff_2">
            <en>Normal</en>
            <de>Normal</de>
            <fr>Normal</fr>
            <pl>Normalna</pl>
            <es>Normal</es>
            <it>Normale</it>
            <cz>Normální</cz>
            <br>Normal</br>
            <uk>Звичайна</uk>
            <ru>Обычная</ru>
            <hu>Normál</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_diff_3">
            <en>Realistic</en>
            <de>Realistisch</de>
            <fr>Réaliste</fr>
            <pl>Realistyczna</pl>
            <es>Realista</es>
            <it>Realistica</it>
            <cz>Realistická</cz>
            <br>Realista</br>
            <uk>Реалістична</uk>
            <ru>Реалистичная</ru>
            <hu>Realisztikus</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_hud_short">
            <en>Show HUD</en>
            <de>HUD anzeigen</de>
            <fr>Afficher HUD</fr>
            <pl>Pokaż HUD</pl>
            <es>Mostrar HUD</es>
            <it>Mostra HUD</it>
            <cz>Zobrazit HUD</cz>
            <br>Mostrar HUD</br>
            <uk>Показувати HUD</uk>
            <ru>Показывать HUD</ru>
            <hu>HUD megjelenítése</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_hud_long">
            <en>Display harvest info</en>
            <de>Ernte-Informationen anzeigen</de>
            <fr>Afficher les infos de récolte</fr>
            <pl>Wyświetl informacje o żniwach</pl>
            <es>Mostrar información de cosecha</es>
            <it>Mostra info sul raccolto</it>
            <cz>Zobrazit informace o sklizni</cz>
            <br>Exibir informações de colheita</br>
            <uk>Відображати інформацію про збір</uk>
            <ru>Отображать информацию о сборе</ru>
            <hu>Betakarítási információk megjelenítése</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_speedlimit_short">
            <en>Speed Limiting</en>
            <de>Geschwindigkeitsbegrenzung</de>
            <fr>Limitation de vitesse</fr>
            <pl>Ograniczenie prędkości</pl>
            <es>Limitación de velocidad</es>
            <it>Limitazione velocità</it>
            <cz>Omezení rychlosti</cz>
            <br>Limitação de velocidade</br>
            <uk>Обмеження швидкості</uk>
            <ru>Ограничение скорости</ru>
            <hu>Sebességkorlátozás</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_speedlimit_long">
            <en>Automatically limit combine speed based on engine load</en>
            <de>Mähdrescher-Geschwindigkeit automatisch basierend auf Motorlast begrenzen</de>
            <fr>Limiter automatiquement la vitesse de la moissonneuse en fonction de la charge du moteur</fr>
            <pl>Automatycznie ogranicz prędkość kombajnu w zależności od obciążenia silnika</pl>
            <es>Limitar automáticamente la velocidad de la cosechadora según la carga del motor</es>
            <it>Limita automaticamente la velocità della mietitrice in base al carico del motore</it>
            <cz>Automaticky omezit rychlost kombajnu podle zatížení motoru</cz>
            <br>Limitar automaticamente a velocidade da colheitadeira com base na carga do motor</br>
            <uk>Автоматично обмежувати швидкість комбайна залежно від навантаження</uk>
            <ru>Автоматически ограничивать скорость комбайна в зависимости от нагрузки</ru>
            <hu>A kombájn sebességének automatikus korlátozása a motor terhelése alapján</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_croploss_short">
            <en>Crop Loss</en>
            <de>Ernteverlust</de>
            <fr>Perte de récolte</fr>
            <pl>Straty plonów</pl>
            <es>Pérdida de cosecha</es>
            <it>Perdita di raccolto</it>
            <cz>Ztráta úrody</cz>
            <br>Perda de colheita</br>
            <uk>Втрати врожаю</uk>
            <ru>Потери урожая</ru>
            <hu>Termésveszteség</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_croploss_long">
            <en>Calculate crop loss when overloaded</en>
            <de>Ernteverlust bei Überlastung berechnen</de>
            <fr>Calculer la perte de récolte en cas de surcharge</fr>
            <pl>Oblicz straty plonów przy przeciążeniu</pl>
            <es>Calcular pérdida de cosecha al sobrecargar</es>
            <it>Calcola perdita di raccolto quando sovraccarico</it>
            <cz>Vypočítat ztrátu úrody při přetížení</cz>
            <br>Calcular perda de colheita quando sobrecarregado</br>
            <uk>Розраховувати втрати врожаю при перевантаженні комбайна</uk>
            <ru>Рассчитывать потери урожая при перегрузке комбайна</ru>
            <hu>Túlterhelés esetén termésveszteség számítása</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_speedindicator_short">
            <en>Speed Indicator</en>
            <de>Geschwindigkeitsanzeige</de>
            <fr>Indicateur de vitesse</fr>
            <pl>Wskaźnik prędkości</pl>
            <es>Indicador de velocidad</es>
            <it>Indicatore velocità</it>
            <cz>Ukazatel rychlosti</cz>
            <br>Indicador de velocidade</br>
            <uk>Показник швидкості</uk>
            <ru>Показатель скорости</ru>
            <hu>Sebességjelző</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_speedindicator_long">
            <en>Display recommended speed indicator in HUD</en>
            <de>Empfohlene Geschwindigkeitsanzeige im HUD anzeigen</de>
            <fr>Afficher l'indicateur de vitesse recommandée dans le HUD</fr>
            <pl>Wyświetl wskaźnik zalecanej prędkości w HUD</pl>
            <es>Mostrar indicador de velocidad recomendada en HUD</es>
            <it>Mostra l'indicatore della velocità consigliata nell'HUD</it>
            <cz>Zobrazit ukazatel doporučené rychlosti v HUD</cz>
            <br>Exibir indicador de velocidade recomendado no HUD</br>
            <uk>Відображати рекомендовану швидкість в HUD</uk>
            <ru>Показывать рекомендуемую скорость в HUD</ru>
            <hu>Ajánlott sebesség megjelenítése a HUD-on</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_units_short">
            <en>Units</en>
            <de>Einheiten</de>
            <fr>Unités</fr>
            <pl>Jednostki</pl>
            <es>Unidades</es>
            <it>Unità</it>
            <cz>Jednotky</cz>
            <br>Unidades</br>
            <uk>Одиниці</uk>
            <ru>Единицы</ru>
            <hu>Mértékegységek</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_units_long">
            <en>Choose measurement system (speed, mass, area)</en>
            <de>Wählen Sie das Messsystem (Geschwindigkeit, Masse, Fläche)</de>
            <fr>Choisissez le système de mesure (vitesse, masse, superficie)</fr>
            <pl>Wybierz system pomiarowy (prędkość, masa, powierzchnia)</pl>
            <es>Elija el sistema de medición (velocidad, masa, área)</es>
            <it>Scegli il sistema di misurazione (velocità, massa, area)</it>
            <cz>Vyberte měrný systém (rychlost, hmotnost, plocha)</cz>
            <br>Escolha o sistema de medição (velocidade, massa, área)</br>
            <uk>Оберіть систему вимірювання (швидкість, маса, площа)</uk>
            <ru>Выберите систему измерения (скорость, масса, площадь)</ru>
            <hu>Mérési rendszer kiválasztása (sebesség, tömeg, terület)</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_unit_metric">
            <en>Metric (km/h, t/h, ha)</en>
            <de>Metrisch (km/h, t/h, ha)</de>
            <fr>Métrique (km/h, t/h, ha)</fr>
            <pl>Metryczny (km/h, t/h, ha)</pl>
            <es>Métrico (km/h, t/h, ha)</es>
            <it>Metrico (km/h, t/h, ha)</it>
            <cz>Metrický (km/h, t/h, ha)</cz>
            <br>Métrico (km/h, t/h, ha)</br>
            <uk>Метричні (км/год, т/год, га)</uk>
            <ru>Метрические (км/ч, т/ч, га)</ru>
            <hu>Metrikus (km/h, t/h, ha)</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_unit_imperial">
            <en>Imperial (mph, ton/h, ac)</en>
            <de>Imperial (mph, ton/h, ac)</de>
            <fr>Impérial (mph, ton/h, ac)</fr>
            <pl>Imperialny (mph, ton/h, ac)</pl>
            <es>Imperial (mph, ton/h, ac)</es>
            <it>Imperiale (mph, ton/h, ac)</it>
            <cz>Imperiální (mph, ton/h, ac)</cz>
            <br>Imperial (mph, ton/h, ac)</br>
            <uk>Імперські (mph, ton/h, ac)</uk>
            <ru>Имперские (mph, ton/h, ac)</ru>
            <hu>Angolszász (mph, tonna/óra, ac)</hu>
        </text>
        
        <text name="rhm_unit_bushels">
            <en>Imperial with Bushels (mph, bu/h, ac)</en>
            <de>Imperial mit Bushels (mph, bu/h, ac)</de>
            <fr>Impérial avec boisseaux (mph, bu/h, ac)</fr>
            <pl>Imperialny z buszelami (mph, bu/h, ac)</pl>
            <es>Imperial con bushels (mph, bu/h, ac)</es>
            <it>Imperiale con bushel (mph, bu/h, ac)</it>
            <cz>Imperiální s bušly (mph, bu/h, ac)</cz>
            <br>Imperial com bushels (mph, bu/h, ac)</br>
            <uk>Імперські з бушелями (mph, bu/h, ac)</uk>
            <ru>Имперские с бушелями (mph, bu/h, ac)</ru>
            <hu>Angolszász bushellel (mph, bu/óra, ac)</hu>
        </text>

        <text name="rhm_reset">
            <en>Reset RH Settings</en>
            <de>RH-Einstellungen zurücksetzen</de>
            <fr>Réinitialiser les paramètres RH</fr>
            <pl>Resetuj ustawienia RH</pl>
            <es>Restablecer config. RH</es>
            <it>Ripristina impostazioni RH</it>
            <cz>Resetovat nastavení RH</cz>
            <br>Restaurar configurações RH</br>
            <uk>Скинути налаштування RH</uk>
            <ru>Сбросить настройки RH</ru>
            <hu>RH beállítások visszaállítása</hu>
        </text>

        <text name="rhm_loss_low">
            <en>LOW</en>
            <de>NIEDRIG</de>
            <fr>FAIBLE</fr>
            <pl>NISKIE</pl>
            <es>BAJO</es>
            <it>BASSO</it>
            <cz>NÍZKÉ</cz>
            <br>BAIXO</br>
            <uk>НИЗЬКІ</uk>
            <ru>НИЗКИЕ</ru>
            <hu>ALACSONY</hu>
        </text>

        <text name="rhm_loss_med">
            <en>MED</en>
            <de>MITTEL</de>
            <fr>MOYEN</fr>
            <pl>ŚREDNIE</pl>
            <es>MEDIO</es>
            <it>MEDIO</it>
            <cz>STŘEDNÍ</cz>
            <br>MÉDIO</br>
            <uk>СЕРЕДНІ</uk>
            <ru>СРЕДНИЕ</ru>
            <hu>KÖZEPES</hu>
        </text>

        <text name="rhm_loss_high">
            <en>HIGH</en>
            <de>HOCH</de>
            <fr>ÉLEVÉ</fr>
            <pl>WYSOKIE</pl>
            <es>ALTO</es>
            <it>ALTO</it>
            <cz>VYSOKÉ</cz>
            <br>ALTO</br>
            <uk>ВИСОКІ</uk>
            <ru>ВЫСОКИЕ</ru>
            <hu>MAGAS</hu>
        </text>
    </l10n>
</modDesc>
